Sleeping is important, but we all know that, right?
睡眠很重要，这一点我们都心知肚明，对吧？
Many people have experienced strange sleeping patterns, weird dreams and a feeling of restlessness and drowsiness during the coronavirus lockdown, despite a good night’s sleep.
新冠疫情封锁期间，许多人即便晚上睡了一觉，还是会出现睡眠规律紊乱、做奇怪的梦、烦躁不安和昏昏欲睡的情况。
So what sort of things can help you to improve your sleep?
那么，有哪些方法可以帮助改善睡眠呢？
There's a plethora of myths related to sleep, some of which can be quite damaging for our health.
关于睡眠，流传着很多不实说法，其中一些还会对健康造成不小的伤害。
Former British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher famously claimed that she only hit the sack for five hours a night.
英国前首相玛格丽特·撒切尔曾有个广为人知的说法，称自己每晚只睡五个小时。
But according to experts this is detrimental to health.
但专家表示，这种作息对健康有害。
Likewise, kipping in front of the TV is another thing to avoid. The bright lights can prevent you from entering deep sleep.
同样，在电视机前打瞌睡也是需要避免的行为，屏幕的强光会阻碍你进入深度睡眠状态。
From a young age we're told to count sheep to help us to nod off, with some choosing to stay in bed to battle with insomnia.
我们从小就被告知，睡不着时可以数绵羊帮助入睡，有些人也会选择躺在床上，对抗失眠的困扰。
However, some experts advise getting up and doing something mindless, like folding socks, to help us get in the mood to catch forty winks.
但有专家建议，这种时候不如起身做点不用费脑子的事，比如叠袜子，反而能帮助我们酝酿睡意，打个小盹。
Psychologist Seth J. Gillihan PhD recommends walking to help in the battle against insomnia.
心理学家塞思·J·吉利汉博士建议，散步有助于对抗失眠。
He talks about a sleep study published in the journal Sleep Health which suggests that those who walk slightly more will experience better quality and duration of sleep.
他提到《睡眠健康》期刊上发表的一项睡眠研究，该研究表明，走路稍多的人，睡眠质量和时长都会更好。
Watching what you eat or drink can also improve the amount of REM, or rapid eye movement you experience.
注意饮食同样能提高快速眼动睡眠的时长。
If you're a snorer, you might also want to take note.
如果你睡觉打鼾，那也需要多加留意。
While most snoring is harmless, it could be a sign of sleep apnoea, with people suffering from the condition more likely to have strokes or heart attacks, irregular heartbeats or high blood pressure.
虽然大多数打鼾并无害处，但这也可能是睡眠呼吸暂停综合征的信号。患有这种病症的人，患上中风、心脏病、心律不齐或高血压的概率会更高。
Finally, a decent nap, or even a power nap, can help you to be more alert, calm and focussed.
最后，好好睡个午觉，哪怕是短暂的小憩，都能让你变得更清醒、冷静、专注。
So while there are some good tips like exercising or folding socks to help us get a good night's sleep, sometimes a good afternoon's sleep can help us tackle the day ahead.
所以说，虽然运动、叠袜子这类方法能帮我们改善夜间睡眠，但有时候，一个舒服的午觉也能帮我们更好地应对接下来的一天。